http://www.silpada.com/l/privacy-policy

Modified on: September 29, 2020
Thank you for visiting Silpada. Your privacy is very important to us. The information below is designed to inform you of what information we collect, why we collect that information and how we use it. We will only share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described below and will never sell your personal information.
When you submit your personal information to us, you are giving us your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We are available to discuss your questions or concerns regarding this Policy and our privacy practices.
We encourage you to check the date of our Privacy Policy each time you visit the website as we sometimes need to change the Privacy Policy to stay in compliance with the various regulations that govern privacy practices.
Browsing our Website
In general, you can browse our Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, some items require you to have an account with Silpada in order to view pricing. In all cases, placing an order requires you to disclose personally identifiable information so that we may properly process and ship your order.
Personally Identifiable Information
Personally identifiable information includes: your name, shipping and billing addresses, telephone number, email address, and credit card and/or banking information.
This information is used to process your order, ship your order, collect payment for your order, comply with applicable provisions of the Patriot Act, communicate with you regarding your order and allow you to receive marketing offers. Silpada does not share this information with third-parties unless it is required to process your order, deliver marketing material or as required by governmental regulation. This information is never sold to third-parties.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
Non-personally identifiable information includes: IP address of your computer, the type of computer or device you are using, etc. that allows us to deliver a positive user experience when shopping on our site as well as to detect and prevent fraud.
Note that the non-personally identifiable information is not linked to any personally identifiable information you submit on our site.
Use of Cookies
We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie enables the shopping cart experience and expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time or is deleted by you.
You are free to decline the use of cookies, however, by declining the use of cookies, you may not be able to use certain features on the Website.
Opting-Out
You may opt-out from receiving marketing material from Silpada. To do so, you may un-subscribe via the link provided in any email you receive from Silpada or by contacting us at 1-800-545-6566 and asking an agent to remove you from our mailing lists. Opting out of receiving marketing materials will not affect our communications with you regarding your orders with us and also does not affect our use of your non-personally identifiable information.
Data Security
Silpada has physical and electronic procedures in place to keep all information collected on our website safe and secure.
Legal Requirements
Silpada will disclose your personal information only when required or compelled to do so in accordance with the law.
